JENNYVER SEZTIANI LUXMAN

Graduated from Multi Data Palembang in 2018 with GPA 3.63. Like to learn a new things from materials and people's experiences, think out of the box, able to communicate well and work with my team. I'm going to contribute well in growth and development of the company by using my skills and my knowledges.



WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2021 - January 2022 PT. World Innovative Telecommunication Palembang (Warehouse Admin)

- Processing all store orders (phone) through the system.
- Calculate all stock (phone) though physical and system.
- Calculate all daily and monthly income.

April 2019 - July 2020 PT. Thamrin Brothers Yamaha Palembang (Marketing & Sales Admin)

- Create internal memo for marketing and sales division.
- Prepare monthly campaign.

June 2018 - January 2019 Bank Central Asia Palembang (Teller)

• Serving customers in depositing money, withdrawing money, deposits, clearing, and others.

CONTACT

- 082282017085
- fenjenjen@gmail.com
- jenjenfenfen, jenny_xg9
- JI. KHA Rasyid Siddik No. 11/220 8 Ulu Seberang Ulu I Palembang 30252

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018 Multi Data Palembang

Bachelor of Information Technology

2011 - 2014 Xaverius 3 Palembang

Senior High School of Science Major

SKILL

Hard Skill

- Microsoft
- MySQL
- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- JQuery
- Node.js

Soft Skill

- Problem Solving
- Team Work

Language

- Indonesia
- English